clayton.net 2018-10-04

# Privacy

rev. 5/17

Download our [Privacy Policy](https://p.widencdn.net/a7izzh/Privacy-Notice) (PDF)

#### FACTS

##### WHAT DO VANDERBILT, HOMEFIRST, CMH, PROPERTIES, AND WIMBLEDON DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

##### Why?

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.

##### What:

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:

  * Social Security number and income
  * Account balances and assets
  * Credit history and credit scores

##### How?

All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information; the reasons Vanderbilt, HomeFirst, CMH, Properties, and Wimbledon choose to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.

#### Reasons we can share your personal information

| 

#### Can you limit this sharing?  
  
---|---  
  
For our everyday business purposes - such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureau.

| 

No  
  
 **For our marketing purposes -**  
to offer our products and services to you

| 

No  
  
 **For joint marketing with other financial companies**

| 

No  
  
 **For our affiliates ' everyday business purposes -**  
information about your transactions and experiences

| 

No  
  
 **For our affiliates ' everyday business purposes -**  
information about your creditworthiness

| 

Yes  
  
 **For our affiliates to market to you**

| 

Yes  
  
 **For nonaffiliates to market to you**

| 

Yes  
  
##### To limit our sharing

  * Call toll-free [877-826-5294](tel:8778265294) -our menu will prompt you through your choices or
  * Visit us online: [http://www.optoutoday.com](http://www.optoutoday.com/)

 _Please note:_  
If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.

However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.

##### Questions?

Call toll-free [877-826-5310](tel:8778265310).

###### Who we are

##### Who is providing this notice

Vanderbilt Mortgage and Finance, Inc. (NMLS #1561)("Vanderbilt"; HomeFirst Agency, Inc. ("HomeFirst"); CMH Homes, Inc. and CMH of KY, Inc. ("CMH"); CMH Properties, Inc. ("Properties"); Wimbledon Realty, LLC and Wimbledon Properties, LLC ("Wimbledon"). In California, HomeFirst does business as HomeFirst Insurance Agency.

###### What we do

##### How do Vanderbilt, HomeFirst, CMH, Properties, and Wimbledon protect my personal information?

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.

##### How do Vanderbilt, HomeFirst, CMH, Properties, and Wimbledon collect my personal information?

We collect your personal information, for example, when you

  * Apply for a loan or apply for insurance
  * Give us your income information or give us your contact information
  * Give us your employment history

We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.

##### Why can't I limit all sharing?

Federal law gives you the right to limit only

  * sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness
  * affiliates from using your information to market to you
  * sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.

What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else? Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.

###### Definitions

##### Affiliates

Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.

  * Our affiliates include financial companies such as Vanderbilt Mortgage and Finance, Inc., HomeFirst Agency, Inc., CMH Homes, Inc., CMH of KY, Inc., CMH Properties, Inc., Wimbledon Realty, LLC, Wimbledon Properties, LLC, and 21st Mortgage Corporation, and nonfinancial companies such as CMH Manufacturing, Inc., and CMH Manufacturing West, Inc.

##### Nonaffiliates

Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.

  * Nonaffiliates we share with can include mortgage companies, insurance companies, direct marketing companies, and nonprofit organizations.

##### Joint Marketing

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.

  * Our joint marketing partners include mortgage companies.

## Other Important Information

California Residents: We will not share your information for joint marketing with other financial companies, or for nonaffiliates to market to you.

Vermont Residents: We will not share your information for joint marketing with other financial companies, for our affiliates' everyday business purposes (information about your creditworthiness), for our affiliates to market to you, or for nonaffiliates to market to you.
